Atri Banerjee

Application Developer

atri.tih@gmail.com

Summary

More than 5 years of experience in the Information Technology industry. Hands on experience on project development. Proficiency in Microsoft Technologies. Experience in working and project managing with overseas clients. Experience in working with multiple teams and projects at a time. Comfortable to work in R&D related jobs. Always interested in learning new technologies.

Core Expertise:

- Asp.Net 3.5,4.0,4.5
- MVC Architecture 3, 4, 5
- Windows Application
- Windows Service
- Web Service
- SQL Server
- Javascript
- Jquery
- JSON
- Ajax
- C#
- Bootstrap
- Project Management
- Handling multiple projects at a time
- Overseas client handling and working with them.

Experience

Application Developer at DreamzTech Solutions Pvt. Ltd

October 2012 - January 2016 (3 years 3 months)

I can work in the following technologies:

Asp.Net 3.5/4.0/4.5,

Asp.Net MVC 3/4/5,

Web API,

Entity Framework,

Windows Form Application,
WPF,
WCF,
Windows Services,
Web Services,
Silverlight,
Sql Server 2005/2008/2012,
My Sql,
Bootstrap,
Geofencing,
Google map etc.
Payment Gateway Integration:
1. Paypal
2. Authorised Dot Net
3. WebPay
4. PaySimple
I do have knowledge and practical working experience in cloud computing:
1. Azure
2. AWS
Software Developer at ILICO Services Ltd April 2012 - October 2012 (6 months) Working in the development of Real Estate Broker Management, using Asp.net 3.5(C#) and Sql Server 2005, Ajax.
Software Developer January 2011 - April 2012 (1 year 3 months)
1. Web application development in Asp.Net 4.0 with C#.
2. Ajax.
3. Sql Server.
•

JavaScript,

JQuery,

Education

Techno India Hooghly under West Bengal University of Technology

M.C.A, Computer Science, 2008 - 2011

Atri Banerjee

Application Developer

atri.tih@gmail.com



Contact Atri on LinkedIn